(this["webpackJsonpprophet-flashcards"]=this["webpackJsonpprophet-flashcards"]||[]).push([[0],{10:function(a,e,t){},11:function(a,e,t){"use strict";t.r(e);var s=t(1),o=t.n(s),i=t(4),n=t.n(i),r=t(2),h=t(0);function l(a){var e=a.flashcard,t=Object(s.useState)(!1),o=Object(r.a)(t,2),i=o[0],n=o[1],l=Object(s.useRef)(),d=Object(s.useRef)();return Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"card ".concat(i?"flip":""),onClick:function(){return n(!i)},children:[Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"front",ref:l,children:[Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"question",children:e.question}),Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"options",children:e.options.map((function(a,e){return Object(h.jsxs)("div",{className:"option",children:["abcd"[e],". ",a]})}))})]}),Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"back",ref:d,children:e.answer})]})}function d(a){var e=a.flashcards;return Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"card-grid",children:e.map((function(a){return Object(h.jsx)(l,{flashcard:a},a.id)}))})}t(10);var c=[{id:1,question:"Who is the first man and Prophet Allah created?",answer:"Adam (AS)",options:["Yusuf (AS)","Ibrahim (AS)","Adam (AS)"]},{id:2,question:"After Allah created Adam (AS), Allah ordered all the angels and jinns to bow down to Adam (AS). Everyone listened except _____ ?",answer:"Shaytaan",options:["Angels","Musa (AS)","Shaytaan"]},{id:3,question:"How did Allah test Adam (AS) and his wife, Hawwa?",answer:"Allah told them not to eat from a tree.",options:["Allah told them not to sleep.","Allah told them not to eat from a tree.","Allah told them not to pray."]},{id:4,question:"Prophet Nuh (AS) told him people to worship only Allah instead of _________.",answer:"Idols",options:["Trees","Animals","Idols"]},{id:5,question:"Allah told Prophet Nuh (AS) to build a big _______ because a flood was coming.",answer:"Boat",options:["Boat","House","Statue"]},{id:6,question:"Which prophet was saved from a hot fire when Allah made the fire cold for him?",answer:"Ibrahim (AS)",options:["Muhammad (SAW)","Yusuf (AS)","Ibrahim (AS)"]},{id:7,question:"Allah told Prophet Ibrahim (AS) to travel with his family until they came to a place near 2 hills called ____",answer:"Safa and Marwa",options:["Makkah and Medina","Safa and Marwa"]},{id:8,question:"When Haajar was looking for water she between Safa to Marwa 7 times. How did Allah reward her?",answer:"Zamzam water started gushing out of the ground.",options:["It started to rain.","She found a river.","Zamzam water started gushing out of the ground."]},{id:9,question:"Allah tested Prophet Ibrahim (AS) by telling him to __________.",answer:"Sacrifice his son.",options:["Sacrifice his son.","Not to eat from a tree.","Talk to Firawn"]},{id:10,question:"Which holiday do we celebrate to remember Prophet Ibrahim (AS) sacrificing a sheep instead of his son?",answer:"Eid-ul-Adha",options:["Eid-ul-Adha","Eid-ul-Fitr","Thanksgiving","New Years"]},{id:11,question:"Which prophet was swallowed by a whale?",answer:"Yunus (AS)",options:["Yunus (AS)","Musa (AS)","Yusuf (AS)"]},{id:12,question:"How did Allah save Musa (AS) and his people from Firawn?",answer:"Allah caused the sea to split.",options:["Allah gave them a boat.","Allah gave them Zamzam water.","Allah caused the sea to split."]},{id:13,question:"Which prophet spoke as a baby?",answer:"Isa (AS)",options:["Isa (AS)","Muhammad (SAW)","Adam (AS)"]},{id:14,question:"What book did Allah reveal to Prophet Muhammad (SAW)?",answer:"Qur'an",options:["Tawrat","Injeel","Qur'an"]}];var u=function(){var a=Object(s.useState)(c),e=Object(r.a)(a,2),t=e[0];return e[1],Object(h.jsxs)(h.Fragment,{children:[Object(h.jsx)("h1",{className:"header",children:"Click on a flashcard to see the answer"}),Object(h.jsx)("div",{className:"container",children:Object(h.jsx)(d,{flashcards:t})})]})};n.a.render(Object(h.jsx)(o.a.StrictMode,{children:Object(h.jsx)(u,{})}),document.getElementById("root"))}},[[11,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.d3cb19fa.chunk.js.map